<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on @TonyHarmelink blogging!</title><link>https://tonyh.dev/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on @TonyHarmelink blogging!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tonyh.dev/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Updating NVIDIA VIBs on ESXi 6.7</title><link>https://tonyh.dev/posts/updating-nvidia-vibs-on-esxi-6.7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyh.dev/posts/updating-nvidia-vibs-on-esxi-6.7/</guid><description>When updating NVIDIA VIBs from 430.46 / 431.79 to 440.87 / 443.05 on ESXi 6.7 I ran into an error message and step that was not listed in the VMware documentation - https://kb.vmware.com/s/article/2033434
The error message was:
vmkload_mod: Can not remove module nvidia: module symbols in use The solution I found to bypass the error was to stop the nvidia-init service by running the command:
/etc/init.d/nvidia-init stop The full process I ran through to update the VIBs on my hosts Maintenance Mode a host to start rolling through.</description></item><item><title>Complete EUC Overhaul with 3D CAD VDI and Workspace ONE Part 1 - Investigating Prior State and Planning</title><link>https://tonyh.dev/posts/complete-euc-overhaul-with-3d-cad-vdi-and-workspace-one-part-1-investigating-prior-state-and-planning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 17:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyh.dev/posts/complete-euc-overhaul-with-3d-cad-vdi-and-workspace-one-part-1-investigating-prior-state-and-planning/</guid><description>The chance rarely comes around to completely rethink and overhaul the end user experience of an organization. Even through bigger upgrades, switching from Windows 7 to Windows 10 for instance, we often try to replicate what the past experience was.
We didn&amp;rsquo;t do that that. We changed almost everything.
Lenovo &amp;amp; HP -&amp;gt; Dell Windows 7 -&amp;gt; Windows 10 Novell Groupwise -&amp;gt; Microsoft Outlook 365 Novell eDirectory -&amp;gt; Windows Active Directory Novell File Server -&amp;gt; Windows DFS Novell ZenWorks -&amp;gt; VMware Workspace ONE UEM VMware Horizon View w/ NVIDIA GRID VMware Workspace ONE Access Cisco CUCM -&amp;gt; Microsoft Teams w/ SIP SBC Prior State When I started at my current employer, the other two team members had spent the past couple years refreshing the backend infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>vEUC Day Presentation: How Horizon Deployed with VCF is allowing Nol-Tec to continue business during COVID-19</title><link>https://tonyh.dev/posts/veuc-day-presentation-how-horizon-deployed-with-vcf-is-allowing-nol-tec-to-continue-business-during-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyh.dev/posts/veuc-day-presentation-how-horizon-deployed-with-vcf-is-allowing-nol-tec-to-continue-business-during-covid-19/</guid><description>I did a presentation at the 2020 Minneapolis Virtual EUC Day yesterday.
The entire thing was pre-recorded so I can easily repost it here for all!
The meat of it is the journey on how a 1 year complete EUC overhaul using Horizon deployed with VMware Cloud Foundation combined with Workspace ONE UEM and Workspace ONE Access allowed us to send everyone home at the drop of a hat and maintain productivity when Covid-19 Stay at Home orders came down.</description></item><item><title> Four Node Bare Metal Kubernetes Raspberry Pi Cluster for about $450</title><link>https://tonyh.dev/posts/four-node-bare-metal-kubernetes-raspberry-pi-cluster-for-about-450/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyh.dev/posts/four-node-bare-metal-kubernetes-raspberry-pi-cluster-for-about-450/</guid><description>I have been thinking of making a homelab for years, but living in a 700 sqft condo I don&amp;rsquo;t have the room for the basement rack of my dreams. A few months ago with the launch of the Raspberry Pi Model 4 B with 4GB of ram I started looking into building a cluster of them for tooling around at home. I found the Pi Dramble which give me the push to build it out for testing Kubernetes and eventually ESXi on ARM.</description></item><item><title>Easy Maintenance Mode vMotion Migration of vGPU Backed VMs</title><link>https://tonyh.dev/posts/easy-maintenance-mode-vmotion-migration-of-vgpu-backed-vms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyh.dev/posts/easy-maintenance-mode-vmotion-migration-of-vgpu-backed-vms/</guid><description>I ran into this issue earlier and didn&amp;rsquo;t find it well documented.
When you put a vGPU host into maintenance mode, the vGPU VMs don&amp;rsquo;t automatically migrate off of the host. Annoying.
It turns out that vMotion uses DRS to evacuate hosts and DRS doesn&amp;rsquo;t automatically act on recommendations for vGPU backed VMs. But we can manually act on the recommendations. Push the apply button in DRS and away it goes.</description></item><item><title>Extract VMware Horizon Client MSI in 5.1</title><link>https://tonyh.dev/posts/extract-vmware-horizon-client-msi-in-5-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyh.dev/posts/extract-vmware-horizon-client-msi-in-5-1/</guid><description>I was working on extracting the MSI for the Horizon Client and noticed that the /x and /extract flags on the VMware Horizon client documentation weren&amp;rsquo;t working for me.
Luckily I did notice a few lines in the log of the installer in my %temp% directory
[6D2C:6D30][2019-09-23T16:11:42]i410: Variable: WixBundleAction = 5 [6D2C:6D30][2019-09-23T16:11:42]i410: Variable: WixBundleElevated = 1 [6D2C:6D30][2019-09-23T16:11:42]i410: Variable: WixBundleInstalled = 1 It&amp;rsquo;s a Wix Bundle installer. These I know how to deal with after exploding and customizing other installers.</description></item><item><title>Workspace ONE: Remove APPX packages from Windows 10 with a custom CSP</title><link>https://tonyh.dev/posts/workspace-one-remove-appx-packages-from-windows-10-with-a-custom-csp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 07:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyh.dev/posts/workspace-one-remove-appx-packages-from-windows-10-with-a-custom-csp/</guid><description>Here is a full CSP method to removing APPX packages from your users environment.
First, get the family names of the packages you want to remove via powershell
Get-AppxPackage | Select Name, PackageFamilyName ![](/uploads/2019-09-01 10_28_59-Window.png)
Determine the packages you wish to remove and add those names into the CSP similar to below, change the CmdID to be unique within your configuration:
&amp;lt;Delete&amp;gt; &amp;lt;CmdID&amp;gt;105&amp;lt;/CmdID&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Item&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Target&amp;gt; &amp;lt;LocURI&amp;gt;./Device/Vendor/MSFT/EnterpriseModernAppManagement/AppManagement/AppStore/Microsoft.Messaging_8wekyb3d8bbwe&amp;lt;/LocURI&amp;gt; &amp;lt;LocURI&amp;gt;./Device/Vendor/MSFT/EnterpriseModernAppManagement/AppManagement/AppStore/Microsoft.MixedReality.Portal_8wekyb3d8bbwe&amp;lt;/LocURI&amp;gt; &amp;lt;LocURI&amp;gt;./Device/Vendor/MSFT/EnterpriseModernAppManagement/AppManagement/AppStore/Microsoft.NetworkSpeedTest_8wekyb3d8bbwe&amp;lt;/LocURI&amp;gt; &amp;lt;LocURI&amp;gt;./Device/Vendor/MSFT/EnterpriseModernAppManagement/AppManagement/AppStore/Microsoft.WindowsMaps_8wekyb3d8bbwe&amp;lt;/LocURI&amp;gt; &amp;lt;LocURI&amp;gt;.</description></item><item><title>VMworld 2019 - My first VMworld</title><link>https://tonyh.dev/posts/vmworld-2019-my-first-vmworld/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyh.dev/posts/vmworld-2019-my-first-vmworld/</guid><description>My first VMworld. It was an awesome time. I highly recommend everyone with an investment or interest in VMware&amp;rsquo;s products to go. I learned so much about how to better use the products I have.
Arriving on Sunday early in the morning made life substantially easier. The registration lines were almost nonexistent, and I was able to get settled in before the Veeam reception at the solutions exchange filled me with beer and a bag full of swag in exchange for hearing about dozens of products.</description></item><item><title>Creating 100s of NTFS permissions with Powershell and DSC</title><link>https://tonyh.dev/posts/creating-100s-of-ntfs-permissions-with-powershell/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 20:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyh.dev/posts/creating-100s-of-ntfs-permissions-with-powershell/</guid><description>Starting at my new employer one of the first major projects to hit implementation phase is a migration of the company file server. The major wrinkle is that the old file server is on Novell, with 25+ years of permission and folder buildup. Millions of files, hundreds of thousands of folders.
The normal Windows to Windows robocopy won&amp;rsquo;t work to preserve permissions, from a Windows perspective the owner and ACL for all files/folders on a Novell share is &amp;lsquo;Everyone.</description></item><item><title>The creation of this blog with Hugo, GitHub Pages, Forestry, and Google Domains</title><link>https://tonyh.dev/posts/the-creation-of-this-blog-with-hugo-github-pages-forestry-and-google-domains/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:57:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonyh.dev/posts/the-creation-of-this-blog-with-hugo-github-pages-forestry-and-google-domains/</guid><description>A coworker asked how I setup this blog so for their and others edification I&amp;rsquo;ll put the steps into writing.
I decided I wanted a super simple blog that would render out to static pages so I could leverage GitHub pages for my hosting, leaving my only expense the domain name. So far I have settled on the stack of Google Domains for my domain, GitHub Pages for my hosting, Hugo for my website framework, and am currently toying with Forestry for content management and creation.</description></item></channel></rss>